# ANDREJA SIMONOVIĆ

Frontend Web Developer



#### **ABOUT ME**

I was born on January 26, 1992. in Belgrade. I am currently working in a real estate agency as an agent. Considering my experience in this agency, I have gained excellent communication skills and work ethic. I am self-taught Web Developer (since 2021). I have: 2 years of Git, HTML, CSS and JavaScript experience, I year of Bootstrap, SASS and Tailwind experience and 0.5 years of TypeScript experience.

## **CONTACT**



andrejasimonovic@protonmail.com



+381 63 17 27 060



https://andreja011.github.io/personal-portfolio-site/#home

## **LANGUAGES**

Serbian



English

## **EXPERIENCE**

## Ana Marasović PR (2019 - today)

Subsidiary of Kaća Lazarevic Nekretnine DOO. I am real estate agent who is also performing various administrative and appraisal jobs. With my Excel skills, I've managed to reduce paperwork time from 2 hours to 35 minutes.

#### Kaća Lazarević nekretnine DOO (2018 - 2019)

In this real estate agency I have been performing various administrative and appraisal tasks.

#### Breza software engineering (2016)

I worked as an internship and trainee, for 5 months. I was studying SQL and MySQL.

## **EDUCATION**

### High business School (2011 - 2016)

Finance accounting and banking.

#### Aviation Academy (2006 - 2010)

Mechanical technican for computer engineering.

Elementary School Ivan Goran Kovačić (1998 - 2006)

## **MY SKILLS**



HTML5



CSS3



SASS



**Tailwind** 



**JavaScript** 



Git

#### **HOBBIES**









Gym Watches

Books

**Moto GP** 

# ANDREJA SIMONOVIĆ

Frontend Web Developer



#### **O MENI**

Rođen sam 26. januara 1992. godine u Beogradu. Trenutno sam zaposlen u agenciji za nekretnine kao agent.
Dugogodišnjim radom u agencijama za nekretine, stekao sam odlične komunikacione veštine i odlične veštine rada sa ljudima. Samouki sam Web Developer (od 2021). Imam: 2 godine Git, HTML, CSS i JavaScript iskustva, 1 godinu Bootstrap, SASS I Tailwind iskustva i 0.5 godine TypeScript iskustva.

### **KONTAKT**



📈 andrejasimonovic@protonmail.com



+381 63 17 27 060



https://andreja011.github.io/personal-portfolio-site/#home

#### **JEZICI**

Srpski



Engleski



#### **ISKUSTVO**

Ana Marasović PR (2019 - danas)

"Ćerka" firma Kaća Lazarevic Nekretnine DOO. Radim kao agent za nekretnine, koji takođe radi na raznim administrativnim poslovima i poslovima procena nepokretnosti. Svojim Excel veštinama sam uspeo da smanjim aministrativni rad sa 2 sata na 35 minuta.

Kaća Lazarević nekretnine DOO (2018 - 2019)

U ovoj agenciji za nekretnine radio sam kao agent, i takođe sam radio na raznim administrativnim poslovima i poslovima procena nepokretnosti.

**Breza software engineering** (2016)

Bio sam na praksi 5 meseci. Za to vreme sam učio SQL i MySQL.

## **OBRAZOVANJE**

Visoka poslovna škola (2011 - 2016)

Finansije računovodstvo i bankarstvo.

Vazduhoplovna akademija (2006 - 2010)

Mašinski tehničar za kompjutersko konstruisanje.

Osnovna Škola Ivan Goran Kovačić (1998 - 2006)

## VEŠTINE







HTML5

CSS3

CACC







**Tailwind** 

JavaScript

Git

## HOBIJI









Teretana

Satovi

**Knjige** 

**Moto GP**